shortfuly.com 2018-10-18

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy:**

This page describes our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal information when you use our services.  
We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy was created with (TermsFeed)  
We use your personal information to provide and improve the service. By using the service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Except as provided in this Privacy Policy, the terms used in the Privacy Policy have the same meaning as in our Terms and Conditions, accessed at [http://shortfuly.com/](https://shortfuly.com/).

**The Site and Third Party Sites:**

This Privacy Policy applies solely to the Site. The Site may contain links to third parties' sites which are not owned or controlled by the Provider. The Provider has no control over, and assumes no responsibility for, the content, privacy policies (if any), or practices of any third parties' sites. You acknowledge that you are responsible for reviewing and understanding the privacy policies (if any) of any third parties' sites you may access through this Site. By using this Site, you release the Provider from any and all liability arising from your use of any third parties' sites to which this Site may link.

Our primary goals in collecting your personal data are to provide and improve the Site and Service and the related features, to administer your subscription and to enable Publishers to enjoy and easily navigate the Site and Service. Below are the types and categories of information we collect.

**Personal Data Collected:**

We collect your personal data in the following ways:

**1\. Login Data**

We collect the information that your browser sends whenever you access our services. This log data may include information such as the Internet Protocol ("IP") address, browser type, browser version, service pages you visit, The time and date of your visit, the time spent on these pages, and other statistics.

**2\. Cookies**

There are instances where we may use cookies to gather information regarding our services in a mathematical collection for our website and our advertisers.

Any information collected will not have any identifying data. It is statistical data about our visitors and how they have used our site. No personal details will be shared that could identify you.

We may assemble information about your common internet use with a cookie file. When used, the cookies are downloaded to your computer automatically. The cookie is stored on the hard drive, with transferred information. The data sought by the cookie helps us improve our website and any service offered to you.

Your browser has the ability to decline cookies. This is done by setting your browser options to decline all cookies. Note: if you do decline the download of cookies, some aspects of our site may not work or allow you access.

Our advertisers may download cookies to which we have no control. If used, these cookies are downloaded by clicking on an advertisement found on our website.

**3\. Protect**

Securing your personal information is very important to us, but keep in mind that no method of transmission over the Internet, or electronic means of storage is 100% safe. While we try to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we can not guarantee its absolute security.

**4\. Third Party Links**

Our Site contains links to other websites. If you choose to visit an advertiser by clicking on a banner ad or other type of advertisement, or click on another third party link, you will be directed to those third parties' websites. The fact that we link to a website or present a banner ad or other type of advertisement is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party, nor is it an endorsement of their privacy or information security policies or practices. We do not exercise control over third parties' websites. These other websites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect personal data or solicit personal information from you. Other sites follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the personal data you submit to them. We encourage you to read the privacy policies (if any) or statements of the other websites you visit.

**5.  Information Accessibility**

We cannot withhold data we collect about you, as per The Data Protection Act 1998. This act provides you with access to any information we may hold on you. If you wish to have access about our data collection on you please pay our fee of ?10. The fee covers our costs for processing your request and getting the data to you. Please use the contact details below to formulate your data access request.

**6\. How to contact us**

If you have any queries regarding your personal data or comments on this Privacy Policy, please email us using the following [Contact Us](mailto:shortfuly@yandex.com).
